# ATSUKI KITADA

# FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

236-838-1813

**✓** canvanvam@gmail.com

**Q** Vancouver, BC

https://atsuki.netlify.app

#### **EDUCATION**

#### College

2023 - Present
Cornerstone International
Community College of Canada
Diploma of Computer Sciences

### University

2015 - 2019 Doshisya University Bachelor's in Law

## SKILLS

**LANGUAGES**: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript

## FRAMEWORKS, LIBRARIES:

NodeJs, ReactJS, NextJS, React Router, Redux, Bootstrap, SASS, TailwindCSS, Framer Motion

**OTHERS**: Supabase, Git, Figma, Canva

#### **PROFILE**

I am a passionate web developer with a strong curiosity for technology and a keen eye for creating beautiful and functional websites. My drive for creativity, problemsolving, and continuous learning sets me apart. I am enthusiastic about contributing my skills and expertise to help businesses and individuals achieve their goals. Let's collaborate to bring your ideas to life and create exceptional web experiences that leave a lasting impression.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICER

# **Civil Aviation Bureau - Accounting Department**

April 2019 - March 2021

- Managed financial and administrative tasks within the accounting department.
- Ensured accuracy and compliance with financial procedures.

# **Civil Aviation Bureau - Human Resources department** *April 2021 - December 2022*

- Led the management of the mutual benefit association for over 6000 employees.
- Oversaw the issuance of insurance cards and verified employees' eligibility for insurance coverage.
- Promoted to team leader, effectively managing and training a team of employees.